So here we have already with everything.
These are the registry keys if you can able to add your malicious executable under this
key, you can able to achieve the persistence.
So this is the way using register TXC, you can add a persistence or we might see in
a log in session, so don't let me show that a red editor, you can if you move to the
registry editor, you can easily get the key, so the key will be, if you want to execute
your malware for a current user, you can use this key, or if you want to execute the
malware across all the users who are logged into the machine, so you can go to this
kind of key.
Basically, most of the threat actors will be targeting this key, you can add whatever
you want, so that's your own mechanism, so in this video, I'll be adding the malicious
of executable that was created by the MS of Venom to this registry, okay, to this registry
and the software Microsoft Windows current version, let me move back to the registry key.
The current version, somewhere Microsoft Windows, here's a current version, you can see,
and here you can see the executable already, run once and run, there is already there
are two keys, won't drive and MS Edge app launch, so my won't drive must might be running,
so if I started my machine, won't drive it automatically executed only once I started
my machine, okay, so let's add our executable in this key, okay, so to add your registry
key, you can use this command, let me take this, and I need to modify this command, so
remember, you can able to add four systems in an administrator mode only, that's why we
have seen the privilege escalation in a previous video, for in a previous session, so let
me add a calc one time, okay, so let me refresh, so here you can see the calculator
get automatically harder, let me delete this, okay, if you want to delete the key, you
can just, you can just, you can instead of, instead of add you can do reds, de, dl, very
close, very close, and I have pressed delete, delete the registry key, very positive chance
I'll be giving us, okay, I have missed the option, slash your, let's see if there is any
mistakes, error, call, close systems, it wasn't able to find a specific registry key or
value, this is the one which I have already executed, let me check it with this one, it's
okay, now the operation get successful, okay, c, we have done a small mistake, drs, s, t,
any, not the key, the key or s, s, s, s, t and c, the key name, so that's why, let me
stay happens, so now we can find the registry key has been automatically get removed, let
me go to, let me edit, here, so my malware was sitting under the key, you first, let's
see, this is my, this is my registry key, and you need to mention slash yes, let me change
the key name, then we execute now, the operation has been completed successfully, let
me, go to the key, so you can see the key, it was pointing to the, a persistent mal.exe,
let me restart my mission now, I'll restart my mission now, and we'll see what will happen,
before that I'll be starting my reverse connection listener, okay, the TTV listener has been
initiated, let's restart that, wait for a few more minutes, once the window is back.
Wait for something, everything needs to be get loaded, once the window is done on,
okay, if you see, here it was asking, whether we need to execute, okay, let's see, okay,
you can execute this persistent smell.exe, if we're giving our run here, so I'll be getting,
I'll be getting a reverse connection, okay, so probably instead of adding, instead of adding
the executable here, you can able to push the PowerShell scripts, okay, to execute, okay,
and that will also be happening, that will also happen on the incidents, so instead of
exe, you can push the PowerShell scripts to the run here registries, and I'll be getting
a reverse connection, so here, I didn't get a reverse connection, let me re verify that,
so either I just, even anything wrong, let me check, 967, okay, see, I did a mistake,
you can see the port has been drawn, so that's a mistake, I did, let me change, 896, okay,
8769, now it will be getting executed, okay, yeah, now, I got a reverse connection,
so if I restart my machine, so the malware will be getting automatically executed, so the mistake
we have done is, we did a wrong port, we have created a malware known port, and we listened
our malware and another port, that's the problem, so let's swap off and I'll again, I'll be
restarting the machine in the next video, so to prove it will be happening, the reverse
connection will be happening, okay, let's swap off from this video and we'll continue our
in discussion now. Next video see you guys bye-bye.